# BHANUTEJA VIVEKANANDAM

## **FULLSTACK DEVELOPER**

Self-starting and resourceful [software developer] with experience implementing front-end and back-end coding. Astute and always-learning designer of user interactions on websites and databases that are sound and easy to use. Proven problem-solver with solid grounding in data-driven applications and concepts.

Communicates clearly with technical and non-technical team

members and promotes drive for customer service.

## **Work History**

2023-12-08 2024-9-28 PYTHON FULL STACK TUTOR IN ASSOSIATE Academy Tirupathi

I teach HTML, CSS, JavaSript, Python, MySql, Django

2020-06 -21 2023-11-31

# Full Stack Developer [software developer]

#### XACTO Services Pvt Ltd, BANGALORE.

- Monitored technical performance of internal systems and gathered information from consumers about program functionality.
- Used software tools in cooperation with continuous integration and test automation and supported software reuse and refactoring.
- Learned new emerging technologies and took initiative to offer technical direction and creative solutions.
- Helped code and test full-stack [Software]based web application software based on Agile Scrum and Kanban approaches.
- Wrote production-ready code with fluency in modern front-end and back-end frameworks.
- Worked with senior developers and designers to implement [Software] using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and PHP.
- Delivered user support to clients to train, educate and answer questions.
- Created powerful Content Management Systems to serve as interface for client.
- Reviewed code to validate structures, assess

#### Contact

#### **Address**

BANGALORE, INDIA 562125

#### Phone

9030500532

#### E-mail

vishwateja2012@gmail.com

#### Web

https://bhanuteja1990.github.i o/portfolio-bhanuteja/

### **Technical Profile**

- Python
- PyTest
- HTML
- JavaScript
- Beautiful soup
- Microsoft PowerPoint
- Git
- Google Workspace
- Microsoft Outlook
- Node.is
- DS
- Selenium
- MongoDB
- GitHub
- Django
- MySQL

### Competencies

Programming

Technical Analysis

Active Listening

Web development projects

security and verify browser, device and operating system compatibility.

Flexible and Adaptable

# Education

2008-05 - Bachelor of Technology: Mechanical Engineering
 2012-06 Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University - TIRUPATHI